Debra Wolford

Junior Full-Stack Web Developer

Ambitious Junior Web Developer with one year of experience. Focused on expanding knowledge and abilities in website design, back end programming and quality assurance. Experience using HTML and CSS, and basic knowledge of Javascript and Python.

Contact

E-mail

debra.wolford@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/debra-wolford-821b52142

www

<u>debrawolford.qithub.io/dw-</u> portfolio/

Skills

HTML

CSS

Python/Django

Javascript

MongoDB

Wordpress

Adobe Premiere and Photoshop

Customer Support

Online Fundraising

Work History

2019-08 -Current

Online Fundraising Creative Assistant

PETA UK, Remote

- Collaborated with senior leadership to identify funding objectives and devise workable development plans.
- Consistently raised sufficient funds through email appeals to stay above budget.

2017-09 -2019-08

PETA Netherlands Projects Coordinator

PETA UK, Remote

- Managed the PETA NL website using Wordpress
- Created content such as blogs and emails
- Managed Twitter and Facebook accounts
- Created social media images and videos, and did voiceovers for videos when necessary
- Occasionally organized demonstrations and billboard campaigns
- Translated text from Dutch to English and English to Dutch

2017-01 -2017-08

PETA Netherlands Membership Coordinator

PETA UK, London, UK

- Monitored the mail, e-mail account, phone, and voicemail, and responded to all queries
- Generated letters and e-mail correspondence in Dutch, including donor updates and acknowledgement letters
- Processed all PETA Netherlands donations and bank statements
- Assisted in coordinating copy and artwork for the Fundraising Department
- Translated text from Dutch to English and English to Dutch

2014-07 -2017-01

Customer Support Representative for Canon UK

Arvato, Venlo

Languages

English

Dutch

- Provided technical product support to customers over the phone and via e-mail
- Handled customer complaints
- Submitted and processed orders for business products
- Employee of the month 06/2015

Education

2019-09 - 2020-11	Diploma in Software Development: Full Stack Web Development
	Code Institute - Remote
2011-08 - 2013-06	BSc Animal Sciences: No Degree
	Wageningen University - Wageningen